So over here as you see we have a new document option. It says welcome. How did you hear about your job pot?
Job pot
Nothing, right?
So let's say
social media, nope
other, right?
So
The artificial intelligence course by
The take of college, right? So
this is the source
that
I
Got to know this tool. I click continue and it says tell us about yourself
Well, I'm a professional, right? So
Master of the dark senator watch tutorial. Okay, I close this one
yep, and
This is actually what we got with a tool, right? So a new document is created for us as you see automatically and
What we can do over here is pretty much a lot. So I'll come here and click delete for this very document that we're in and
I
click on jat pot to jot bots to
Get back to the home page. So as you see it says choose an option to start writing
We can click on new generation to start with a first draft or we can click on new document to receive AI
Helping us as writer